Pamela Digby Churchill Hayward Harriman Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: General Correspondence, 1951-1995 (Box I:35-I:180)
  - Alphabetical File, 1951-1995 (Box I:35-I:158)
    - Montgomery, Harle and Kenneth F., 1983-1993
    - Morgan, Edward P., 1971-1992
    - Morocco, 1993
    - Mrazek, Robert J., 1982-1992
    - Muskie, Edmund S. and Jane, 1970s-1989
    - "Nac-Neu" general, (10 folders)
    - "New-Nug" general, (5 folders) (Box I:117)
    - National Abortion Rights Action League, 1990-1992
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1987-1993
    - National Association for the Southern Poor, 1983-1988
    - National Audubon Society, 1982
    - National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, 1985-1991, (2 folders)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984-1990
    - National Federation of Democratic Women, 1986-1990 (Box I:118)
    - National Gallery of Art
      - 1973-1985, (7 folders)
      - 1986-1989, (8 folders) (Box I:119)
      - 1990-1993, (8 folders) (Box I:120)
    - National Mental Health Association, 1980-1991, (5 folders) (Box I:121)
    - National Museum of Women in the Arts, Washington, D.C., 1988-1989
    - National Symphony Orchestra, 1987-1990
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1984-1992, (2 folders)
    - National Wildflower Research Center, 1982-1993, (5 folders) (Box I:122)
    - National Women's Political Caucus, 1976-1978
    - Network for Charitable Giving, 1990
    - New Republic, 1988
    - New York Botanical Garden, New York, N.Y., 1986-1987
    - New York City Ballet, 1979-1983 (Box I:123)
    - New York Hospital, New York, N.Y., 1978-1992
    - New York Public Library, New York, N.Y., 1988-1993
    - NHK Japan Broadcasting Corp., 1984
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1988
    - Nuclear test ban, 1986-1987
    - "Nuclear War" film, 1979
    - Nunn, Sam, 1981-1992
    - "O" general, (5 folders)
    - Oatlands historic property, Leesburg, Va. (Box I:124)
      - 1981-1987, (6 folders)
      - 1988, (1 folder) (Box I:125)
      - 1989-1993, (4 folders)
    - Ohio State University, Columbus, Ohio, Historic Costume and Textiles Collection donation, 1991-1993
    - Olympics, 1989
    - Order of St. John of Jerusalem, 1992
    - "Pab-Pap" general, (4 folders)
    - "Par-Plo" general, (16 folders) (Box I:126)
    - "Po-Py" general, (8 folders) (Box I:127)
    - Pakistan, 1992
    - Panama Canal Treaty, 1977-1978, (2 folders)
    - Paris, France, United States embassy, 1977-1979
    - Parliamentarians for Global Action, 1985-1993
    - Pavilion Opera, 1988
    - Peace Links, Women Against Nuclear War, 1983-1992, (4 folders) (Box I:128)
    - Pelosi, Nancy, 1983-1993
    - Pepper, Claude and Mildred, 1984-1989
    - Piedmont Environmental Council, 1988-1989
    - Piedmont Fox Hounds, 1984
    - Pincus, Walter and Ann, 1989-1991
    - Planned Parenthood, Washington, D.C., 1989-1992
    - Pollin, Irene and Abe, 1980-1992
    - Population Crisis Committee, 1989
    - Positive Spin Foundation, 1988-1989
    - Powell, Louis F., Jr., 1992 (Box I:129)
    - "Q" general
    - Quinn, Thomas, 1990-1991
    - "Rab-Roc" general, (12 folders)
    - "Rod-Rus" general, (19 folders) (Box I:130)
    - Raiser, C. Victor, II, 1984-1992 (Box I:131)
    - Ratner, Ellen, 1992
    - Reading Is Fundamental, 1983-1984
    - Recombinant DNA legislation, 1977-1978
    - Redford, Robert, 1985, undated
    - Reid, Harry, 1986-1990
    - Rich, Bill, 1980-1993, (4 folders)
    - Richards, Ann, 1988-1991 (Box I:132)
    - Ripley, Marie L., 1987-1988
    - Rivlin, Alice M., 1986-1992
    - Robb, Charles S. and Lynda Bird, 1976-1991, (2 folders)
    - Robert F. Kennedy Memorial Awards, 1988
    - Rockefeller, John D., IV, and Sharon, 1972-1992, (2 folders)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance, 1979-1991
    - Rockefeller University, New York, N.Y.
      - Board of trustees
        - Meetings
          - 1979-1982, (3 folders)
          - 1983-1986, (10 folders) (Box I:133)
          - 1987-1989, (11 folders) (Box I:134)
          - 1990
            - June
            - Nov. (Box I:135)
          - 1991-1993, (6 folders)
        - Nominating committee, 1982-1992, (12 folders)
      - Miscellany (Box I:136)
        - 1978-1987, (8 folders)
        - 1988
          - Jan.-Sept.
          - Oct.-Dec. (Box I:137)
        - 1989-1993, (6 folders)
      - Printed material, 1986, (2 folders)
      - University council, 1976-1980 (Box I:138)
    - Rohatyn, Felix G. and Elizabeth F., 1981-1992
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, My Day, 1988
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr., 1975-1990
    - Roosevelt, Selwa, 1986-1990
    - Royal Horticultural Society, 1980-1991
    - Royal National Theatre, London, England, 1991
    - Rudenstine, Angelica and Neil L., 1991-1993
    - Ruhfus, Jurgen, 1988
    - "Sal-Schl" general, (7 folders)
    - "Schm-Sik" general, (14 folders) (Box I:139)
    - "Sil-Spie" general, (17 folders) (Box I:140)
    - "Spit-Sz" general, (16 folders) (Box I:141)
    - Savoyka, Lydia, 1977-1989 (Box I:142)
    - Sawyer, Diane, 1983-1988, undated
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr., and Alexandra, 1972-1993, (3 folders)
    - Seitz, Raymond, 1989-1993
    - Selin, Nina and Ivan, 1990-1992
    - Sevier house, Washington, D.C., 1992
    - Sheinbaum, Stanley K., 1989
    - Shorenstein, Walter H., 1982-1991, undated
    - Shrum, Robert, 1984-1992, undated
    - Shulman, Marshall Darrow and Colette
      - 1977-1987
      - 1988-1993 (Box I:143)
    - Simon, Paul (1928-2003), 1982-1992
    - Simon, Paul (1941- ), 1989-1990
    - Singapore, 1988
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1986-1991
    - Sorensen, Gillian Martin and Theodore C., 1981-1992
    - Southern Accents, 1990
    - Southern Center for International Studies, 1977
    - Soviet Union and former Soviet Union
      - Aganbegyan, Abel, 1988
      - American-Russian Cultural Cooperation Foundation, 1992-1993
      - Andropov, Yuri, 1984
      - Arbatov, Georgy, 1989
      - Barenboim, Grigoriy, 1990
      - Carnegie Corp., 1985
      - Central Committee theses, Nineteenth All-Union Party Conference, 1988
      - Clippings, 1958-1992
      - Correspondence, general, 1976-1993
      - Dobrynin, Anatolii Fedorovich and Irina, 1975-1990 (Box I:144)
      - Dubinin, Yuri V., 1986-1990
      - Eagleburger, Lawrence S., 1992
      - Economic assistance, 1992
      - Events in Washington, D.C., 1991
      - Freedom Support Act, 1992
      - Glastnost, 1987-1988
      - Gorbachev, Mikhail Sergeevich, 1985-1991
      - Gorbachev, Mikhail Sergeevich and Raisa Maksimovna, state visit, 1987
        - Briefing book
        - Luncheon for Raisa Gorbachev, hosted by Harriman
          - Background and planning, (2 folders)
          - Clippings
          - Correspondence
          - Photograph planning
          - Photographs, (1 folder) (Box I:145)
          - Press materials
        - Other materials
        - Soviet embassy events, Dec. 8-9
        - State Department luncheon, Dec. 9
      - Great Britain-USSR Association, 1984
      - Harvard-Columbia Arden House Conference on U.S.-Russian Relations, 1982-1987
      - Linton, Leonard, Perestroika: How to Fix It, 1992
      - Medical aid request, 1991
      - Moscow, 1991-1992
      - Postcards, 1976, undated
      - Primakov, Yevegeniy, 1989-1991
      - Russia for Sale: The Rough Road to Capitalism documentary, 1991-1992
      - Sakharov, Andrei, 1988 (Box I:146)
      - Soviet republics and capitals, 1992
      - Statements, 1982-1990
      - Szporluk, Roman, 1992
      - United States Congress-Russian Parliament Exchange Program, 1992
      - United States diplomacy toward the Commonwealth of Independent States, 1992
      - United States-Russian Business Summit, Washington, D.C., 1992, (2 folders)
      - Women in the Soviet Union, 1987
      - World Charitable Action, 1991
      - Writings, 1983-1988
      - Yavlinsky, Grigory, 1991
    - Spain '92 Foundation, 1991-1992
    - Spanning the Century: The Life of W. Averell Harriman, 1992
    - Spaso House, Moscow, Soviet Union, 1987-1990 (Box I:147)
    - Squier, Prudence, 1986-1993
    - Stallings, Richard, 1988-1991
    - Stamas, Steve, 1991
    - Stanford University, Stanford, Calif., Committee for Art, 1981
    - Statue of Liberty Selection Committee, 1985
    - Stevens, George, Jr. and Elizabeth Guest, 1979, 1988-1992, undated
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1981-1983
    - Strauss, Robert S., 1973-1992
    - Sturua, Melor, 1990
    - Sullivan, Leonard, 1986-1991
    - Sun Valley, Idaho
      - 1981-1990, (3 folders)
      - 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box I:148)
    - Sun Valley Center for the Arts and Humanities, Sun Valley, Idaho, 1976-1978
    - Sun Valley Hospital, Sun Valley, Idaho, 1984
    - Sundlun, Bruce, 1984-1992
    - Swiers, Peter, 1975-1992, (2 folders)
    - Symington, James W., 1984-1992
    - "Ta-Te" general, (5 folders)
    - "Th-Ty" general, (14 folders) (Box I:149)
    - Tarnoff, Peter, 1987-1992, undated
    - Tax Reform Act, 1986-1988
    - Telegrams sent, 1992
    - Terry, Mary Sue, 1985-1992
    - Thank-you letters, 1982-1987, (2 folders)
    - Thomas, Clarence, 1991 (Box I:150)
    - Tree, Marietta, 1972-1990
    - Truman, Harry S., 1983-1992
    - Tuchman, Barbara, 1977, 1989
    - Turk, Helmut, 1993
    - "U" general, (3 folders)
    - Udall, Thomas, 1988
    - Udall Center for Studies in Public Policy, University of Arizona, Tucson, Ariz., 1988-1989
    - UNICEF ball, 1986-1987
    - Union Pacific Railroad, 1985-1986
    - United Negro College Fund, 1983
    - University of Idaho, Moscow, Idaho, Boyd and Grace Martin Institute of Human Behavior, 1984
    - University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif., Washington Politics Program, 1985
    - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Va., White Burkett Miller Center of Public Affairs, 1982-1986
    - Upward Fund, Inc., 1977-1989, (2 folders)
    - "V" general, (6 folders) (Box I:151)
    - Van Der Kemp, Gerald and Florence, 1972-1978, 1991-1993
    - Vance, Cyrus R., and family, 1973-1991
    - Virginia Council of Higher Education, 1987
    - Virginia Fall Races, 1982-1989
    - Virginia-Maryland Regional College of Veterinary Medicine, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va., 1981-1983
    - Virginia Outdoors Foundation, 1988-1989
    - Voice Foundation, 1986-1987
    - "Wac-Walsh" general, (3 folders)
    - "Walter-Whis" general, (14 folders) (Box I:152)
    - "Whitaker-Woods" general, (14 folders) (Box I:153)
    - "Woodward-Wyn" general, (2 folders) (Box I:154)
    - Walker, O. Mallory and Diana, 1983, 1991-1993, undated
    - Waller, Athlyn and Charlotte, 1977-1979
    - Washington Association for Television and Children, 1975-1977
    - Washington, Harold, mayoral fund, 1985-1987
    - Washington Hospice Society, 1978-1980
    - Washington International Horse Show, 1983-1989
    - Washington Project for the Arts, 1983-1989
    - Waterford Foundation, 1983-1991
    - Waterhouse, Hugo and Caroline, 1975-1976 (Box I:155)
    - Watson, Thomas J., Jr., 1978-1992
    - Weddington, Sarah, 1980-1985
    - Western Development Corp., 1992
    - Westheimer, Nancy, 1981-1990, undated
    - WETA television and radio, 1986-1990
    - White House Conference on Families, 1980
    - White House Endowment Fund, 1990
    - White House fellows, 1988-1992
    - White House Preservation Fund, 1979-1981, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box I:156)
    - Whitehead Institute, 1991
    - Who's Who of American Women, 1982-1985
    - Wilder, Lawrence Douglas, 1989-1993
    - Williams, J. D., 1981-1986
    - Winter, William F., 1981-1984
    - Wirth, Timothy E., 1986-1992, (2 folders)
    - Women's Foreign Policy Council, 1990
    - Woodrow Wilson Center, 1990-1993, (2 folders)
    - Woods, Harriett, 1982-1991 (Box I:157)
    - World Rehabilitation Fund, 1976-1989, (7 folders)
    - Wright, James C., Jr., 1980-1989 (Box I:158)
    - Wynn, William, 1981-1989
    - "X" general
    - Xanthaky, Ted, 1971-1977
    - "Y" general
    - Yale University, New Haven, Conn., 1983-1989
    - Young, Andrew, 1978-1987
    - "Z" general
    - Zahedi, Ardeshir, 1973-1977
    - Zinberg, Dorothy, 1974-1993, (2 folders)
    - Unidentified, 1973-1992, undated
  - Chronological File, 1978-1993 (Box I:158-I:180)
    Primarily copies of outgoing correspondence, with some incoming correspondence particularly for the later period.
    Arranged chronologically by date of letter.
    - 1978-1979, (4 folders) (Box I:158)
    - 1980-1981, (13 folders) (Box I:159)
    - 1982
      - Jan.-Mar., (4 folders)
      - Apr.-Dec., (11 folders) (Box I:160)
    - 1983 (Box I:161)
      - Jan.-June, (9 folders)
      - July-Dec., (6 folders) (Box I:162)
    - 1984
      - Jan., (2 folders)
      - Feb.-Aug., (9 folders) (Box I:163)
      - Sept.-Dec., (6 folders) (Box I:164)
    - 1985
      - Jan.-July, (5 folders)
      - Aug.-Nov., (8 folders) (Box I:165)
      - Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:166)
    - 1986
      - Jan.-Apr., (7 folders)
      - Apr.-Oct., (10 folders) (Box I:167)
      - Oct.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box I:168)
    - 1988
      - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
      - Feb.-Apr., (7 folders) (Box I:169)
      - May-Dec., (8 folders) (Box I:170)
    - 1989
      - Jan.
      - Feb.-Nov., (12 folders) (Box I:171)
      - Dec. (Box I:172)
    - 1990
      - Jan.-Aug., (9 folders)
      - Sept.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box I:173)
    - 1991
      - Jan.-June, (7 folders)
      - July-Dec., (6 folders) (Box I:174)
    - 1992
      - Jan.-Sept., (10 folders)
      - Sept.-Nov., (10 folders) (Box I:175)
      - Nov.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box I:176)
    - 1993
      - Set 1
        - Jan.-Apr., (6 folders)
        - Apr.-May, (7 folders) (Box I:177)
      - Set. 2
        - Jan., (2 folders)
        - Feb.-Apr., (9 folders) (Box I:178)
        - Apr.-May, (9 folders) (Box I:179)
        - June-Dec., (10 folders) (Box I:180)
- Part I: Ambassadorial File, 1992-1997 (Box I:181-I:208)
  Correspondence, confirmation hearing briefings, swearing-in ceremony planning files, speeches and writings, copies of official records, media summaries, scheduling and travel records, financial disclosure reports, eulogies, call lists, notes, photographs, an inventory, and printed matter.
  - Alphabetical correspondence file (Box I:181)
    - 1993
      - A-H See also Classified, (7 folders)
      - I-T, (8 folders) (Box I:182)
      - U-Z, (2 folders) (Box I:183)
    - 1994
      - A-F, (6 folders)
      - G-R, (9 folders) (Box I:184)
      - S-Z, (4 folders) (Box I:185)
    - 1995
      - A-C, (3 folders)
      - D-P, (10 folders) (Box I:186)
      - R-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:187)
    - 1996
      - A-Bo, (2 folders)
      - Br-H, (7 folders) (Box I:188)
      - I-P, (8 folders) (Box I:189)
      - R-V, (8 folders) (Box I:190)
      - W-Z, (2 folders) (Box I:191)
    - 1997
      - A-R, (16 folders)
      - S-Z, (5 folders) (Box I:192)
  - Birthday, 1994, undated
  - Call lists, 1993-1997, (6 folders)
  - Christmas cards and thank-you letters
    - 1993-1995, (3 folders)
    - 1996 (Box I:193)
  - Churchill, Winston, biographers and ancestry, 1993-1996
  - Confirmation hearings, 1993, (4 folders)
  - Council of American Ambassadors, 1993
  - Declined speaking requests, 1994-1996, (2 folders) (Box I:194)
  - Eulogies on her death, 1997
  - Harriman Institute, 1994-1996, undated
  - Hotels, 1993-1996, (2 folders)
  - Media summaries, 1995
  - Nomination, press, 1993 (Box I:195)
  - Notes
    - Notebooks, 1995-1997, undated
    - Personal, 1993-1996, undated
  - Official records (copies)
    - Defense Department, 1995
    - Health and Human Services, Department of, 1994
    - State Department
      - 1992-1993, (3 folders)
      - 1994, (2 folders) (Box I:196)
      - 1995
        - Jan.-Aug.
        - Sept.-Dec. (Box I:197)
      - 1996
        - Jan.-May, (2 folders)
        - June-Nov. (Box I:198)
  - Personal chronological file
    - 1992-1994, (5 folders)
    - 1995, (5 folders) (Box I:199)
    - 1996
      - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
      - Mar.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box I:200)
    - 1997, Jan.
  - Personal data, 1993-1994
  - Photographs, 1994-1996, undated, (2 folders)
  - Residences
    - Ambassador's residence, Paris, France, annual inventory, 1996
    - Georgetown, D.C., 1993
    - Sun Valley, Idaho, 1993-1995
    - Willow Oaks estate, Middleburg, Va., 1993-1996 (Box I:201)
  - Resignation letters, 1993
  - Scheduling
    - Appointment books, notes, and loose material, 1993-1997, (4 folders)
    - Binders and printouts
      - 1993
      - 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box I:202)
      - 1995-1997, (3 folders) (Box I:203)
    - Card file See Part I: Oversize
  - School children's mail, 1996-1997, undated
  - Speeches, remarks, and written texts
    - Log, 1993-1996
    - Master sets (Box I:204)
      - Set 1
        - Nos. 1-150, 1993-1994, (3 folders)
        - Nos. 151-307, 1995-1996, (3 folders) (Box I:205)
      - Set 2 (incomplete), 1994 (Box I:206)
  - Swearing-in ceremony, 1993, (3 folders)
  - Travel vouchers
    - 1993
    - 1994-1997, (3 folders) (Box I:207)
  - Trips
    - Inauguration, Washington, D.C., 1997
    - Official, 1993-1995
    - Personal, 1993-1996, (2 folders)
    - Working file, 1994 (Box I:208)
  - Washington, D.C., office files
    - Chronological file, 1993-1997, (3 folders)
    - Financial disclosure reports, 1993-1996, undated, (4 folders)
    - State Department forms, 1993
- Part I: Speeches and Writings, 1973-1992 (Box I:209-221)
  Largely drafts and final copies of speeches and writings, principally articles and op-ed pieces.
  Arranged as speeches and writings. Speeches include a master set of file copies and individual files containing drafts and related material. The contents of both the binders and the files are arranged chronologically by date of delivery. Writings are arranged chronologically by date of article. A draft novel by John Bowles, IV, is filed at the end.
  - Speeches (Box I:209)
    - Binders with master set of speeches
      - 1981-1984, (6 folders)
      - 1985
        - Jan.-Aug., (2 folders)
        - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box I:210)
      - 1987-1992, (6 folders)
    - Files
      - 1973, Sept. 20, introduction, Robert S. Strauss, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
      - 1975
        - Nov. 3, introduction, Charles Collingwood, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - Dec. 12, dedication, New York Hospital Pediatric Clinical Research Center, New York, N.Y. (Box I:211)
      - 1976, June 23, Eden Day, Annapolis, Md.
      - 1977, Feb. 17, introduction, Midge Costanza, Woman's National Democratic Club
      - 1978, Jan. 11, introduction, Margaret Truman Daniel, Woman's Suburban Democratic Club, Silver Spring, Md.
      - 1979
        - Mar. 26, Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee dinner, Dallas, Tex.
        - Nov. 1, Toledo Museum of Art, Toledo, Ohio
      - 1980
        - May 20, award, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - June 20, Salute to Rosalynn Carter, introduction of head table guests, National Mental Health Association
      - 1981
        - Apr. 13, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - Apr. 30, Democrats for the 80's press conference
        - May 28, Democrats for the 80's dinner, Chicago, Ill.
        - June 30, address to congressional interns
        - Oct. 21, "The Road Back," United Democratic Women's Club of Maryland, Baltimore, Md.
      - 1982
        - Apr. 22, Democratic National Committee Issues Forum, Washington, D.C.
        - June 24, release of the Democratic Fact Book, Philadelphia, Pa.
        - Sept. 1, Wall Street Club luncheon, New York, N.Y.
        - Sept. 22, Democratic House and Senate Council meeting
        - Oct. 28, Winston Churchill Memorial and Library, Westminster College, luncheon, New York, N.Y.
        - Dec. 6, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - Dec. 15, training seminar for incumbent Democratic senators, Easton, Md.
      - 1983 (Box I:212)
        - Feb. 28, Democratic Celebration event, Washington, D.C.
        - Mar. 10, dinner honoring Walter H. Shorenstein, San Francisco, Calif.
        - Mar. 18, Presidential Classroom for Young Americans, Alexandria, Va.
        - Mar. 22, testimony before House Committee on Education and Labor
        - Mar. 29 and Apr. 7, Host Committee, 1984 Democratic National Convention, Washington, D.C.
        - Apr. 23, Jefferson-Jackson breakfast, Raleigh, N.C., (2 folders)
        - May 1, Jay P. Altmayer dinner, Mobile, Ala.
        - May 2, Jackson, Miss., breakfast and luncheon
        - May 10, World Rehabilitation Fund Tribute Dinner, New York, N.Y.
        - Aug. 24, Wall Street Club luncheon, New York, N.Y.
        - Sept. 19, speech about a meeting with Yuri Andropov, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box I:213)
        - Sept. 24, West Virginia Federation of Democratic Women, Martinsburg, W.Va., (2 folders)
        - Sept. 26, Impact '84: National Leadership Conference for Democratic Women, Washington, D.C., (2 folders)
        - Oct. 3, National Capital United Negro College Fund Award, Washington, D.C.
        - Dec. 5, Democratic Presidential Trust Dinner, Washington, D.C. (Box I:214)
        - Dec., Fauquier County, Va., speech on fiscal responsibility
      - circa 1983, remarks on the Democrats for the 80's
      - 1984
        - Jan., notes for speech on the Democrats for the 80's
        - Feb. 27, Salute to Democratic Governors dinner, Washington, D.C.
        - May 15, New York Stock Exchange luncheon, New York, N.Y.
        - June 2, honorary degree, Columbia College, Chicago, Ill.
        - June 8, garden party, Washington, D.C.
        - June 14, Committee for National Security, Third Women's Leadership Conference, Washington, D.C., (2 folders)
        - June, remarks on the New Right manual and the Democratic Fact Book
        - July 19, Democratic National Convention, San Francisco, Calif.
        - Aug. 28, dedication, W. Averell Harriman State Office Building Campus, Albany, N.Y.
        - Oct. 2, Benefit for Democratic Senators and Challengers, New York, N.Y.
        - Oct. 21, Loudoun County Democratic Committee Harvest Dinner, Middleburg, Va.
        - Nov. 30, Democratic Wives Forum, Washington, D.C. (Box I:215)
        - Various introductions, including those for Howell Heflin, Walter F. Mondale, and William F. Winter
      - 1985
        - Jan. 29, Democratic National Committee executive directors meeting, Washington, D.C.
        - Mar. 14, remarks at a breakfast
        - Apr. 24, Senate Majority '86 dinner, Washington, D.C.
        - May 11, American Cancer Society annual ball, Washington, D.C.
        - May 15, Association of American Foreign Service Women, Washington, D.C., (2 folders)
        - May 28 [?], remarks on the Democrats for the 80's and the Senate race in 1986, Los Angeles, Calif.
        - June 12, Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
        - June 22, Senate Majority '86 Dinner, Los Angeles, Calif.
        - Aug. 26, Hubert H. Humphrey Award, Democratic-Farmer- Labor Party, Minneapolis, Minn.
        - Sept. 11, introduction, Mary Sue Terry
        - Sept. 12, National Mental Health Association, Washington, D.C.
        - Sept. 23, Gerald L. Baliles fund-raiser
        - Oct. 1, introduction, Harriett Woods
        - Oct. 16, Women Making History event, Washington, D.C. (Box I:216)
        - Oct. 18, Senate Majority '86 reception and dinner, Chicago, Ill.
        - Oct. 22, New York Horticultural Society lunch, New York, N.Y.
        - Nov. 4, John V. Evans, fund-raiser, Washington, D.C.
        - Nov. 6, introduction, Paul Sarbanes, Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C.
        - Nov. 13, Dallas, Tex., event
      - 1986
        - Jan. 26, opening of the Harry Hopkins Papers, Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., (2 folders)
        - Apr. 15, Brook Hollow Country Club dinner, Dallas, Tex.
        - Apr. 22